Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project management records, circa 2004-2005; Accession 2006-A-095; 24.25; (29 boxes)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine, IE, RM 25, LAB, Barkin Andrade Architects PC- DOC Y100; 011130-03 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine, IE, RM 25, LAB, Taulman Constr- Change Order; 011130-03 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine, IE, RM 25, LAB, Taulman Constr- Contract for the Contruction Phase; 011130-03 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - YPB ELEVATOR INSTALLATION UPGRADE, Chapel Construction; 011114-02 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C-Wing 4th Floor Renovations, Taulman Constr Co Inc-Change Order 1; 011205-01 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C-Wing 4th Floor Renovations, Taulman Constr Co Inc-Change Order 2; 011205-01 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C-Wing 4th Floor Renovations, Taulman Constr Co Inc-Pre-Constr Phase Services Contract; 011205-01 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C-Wing 4th Floor Renovations, Taulman Constr Co Inc-Constr Phase Contract; 011205-01 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C-Wing 4th Floor Renovations, Svigals + Partners- Change Authorization; 011205-01 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C-Wing 4th Floor Renovations, Svigals + Partners- Agreement for Arch Services; 011205-01 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - 52 Hillhouse Ave Exterior Rehab, Giordano Constr Co Inc-Certification of Substantial Compl; 011221-01 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 52 Hillhouse Ave Exterior Rehab, Giordano Constr Co Inc-Change Order; 011221-01 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 52 Hillhouse Ave Exterior Rehab, Helpern Architects- Change Authorization; 011221-01 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 52 Hillhouse Ave Exterior Rehab, Helpern Architects- Agreement for Arch Services; 011221-01 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 52 Hillhouse Ave Exterior Rehab, Giordano Constr Co Inc- Change Order; 011221-01 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 52 Hillhouse Ave Exterior Rehab, Giordano Constr Co Inc- Owner and Contractor Contract; 011221-01 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Kline Biology Tower-Concourse, Sordoni Skanska- Certificate of Substantial Completion; 020131-01 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Kline Biology Tower-Concourse, Sordoni Skanska- Certificate of Substantial Completion; 020207-01 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Kline Biology Tower-Concourse, Sordoni Skanska- Contract for Construction Phase; 020207-01 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - BML 40, Barkin Andrade Architects PC- Change Authorization; 020213-02 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - BML 40, Barkin Andrade Architects PC- Owner and Architect Agreement; 020213-02 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - BML 40, Taulman Construction- Change Order; 020213-02 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - BML 40, Taulman Construction- Contract for Construction; 020213-02 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - OML ROOF REPLACEMENT, Giordano Const. Co. Inc.-Change Order 2 and 4; 020214-01 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - OML ROOF REPLACEMENT, Giordano Const. Co. Inc.-Abbreviated Agreement; 020214-01 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - OML ROOF REPLACEMENT, Giordano Const. Co. Inc.-Change Order 1; 020214-11 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - OML ROOF REPLACEMENT, Giordano Const. Co. Inc.-Change Order 3; 020214-11 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - OML ROOF REPLACEMENT, Giordano Const. Co. Inc.-Change Order; 020214-11 (Box 4)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine CE-1 OFFICE RENOVATION, Barkin Andrade- Change Authorization; 020219-01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine CE-1 OFFICE RENOVATION, Barkin Andrade- Agreement for Architect Services; 020219-01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine CE-1 OFFICE RENOVATION, Chapel Construction- Change Order; 020219-01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine CE-1 OFFICE RENOVATION, Chapel Construction- Contract for Construction Phase; 020219-01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - OML Window Replacement, Giordano Const.- Change Order; 020219-02 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - OML Window Replacement, Giordano Const.- Owner and Contractor Contract; 020219-02 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine IE 14/16 RENOVATION, Charles Beckman Swanson Architects-Change Authorization; 020227-01 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine IE 14/16 RENOVATION, Chapel Construction- Change Order; 020227-01 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine IE 14/16 RENOVATION, Chapel Construction- Constract for Construction Phase; 020227-01 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - PHELPS HALL WINDOW REPLACEMENT, Giordano Const.- Change Order; 020305-01 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - PHELPS HALL WINDOW REPLACEMENT, Giordano Const.- Owner and Contractor Contract; 020305-01 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Basement Clinic Renovation, Charles Beckman Swanson Architects- Doc Y 130-A; 020308-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Basement Clinic Renovation, Charles Beckman Swanson Architects- Doc Y100; 020308-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Basement Clinic Renovation, Chapel Construction-Change Order; 020308-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Basement Clinic Renovation, Chapel Construction- Contract for Construction Phase; 020308-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I-100, 100A, 110 Renovation, Baddidge Faciltiies and Construction- Change Order; 020325-01 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I-100, 100A, 110 Renovation, Baddidge Faciltiies and Construction- Doc Y-202; 020325-01 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I-100, 100A, 110 Renovation, Baddidge Faciltiies and Construction- Doc Y100; 020325-01 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Yale Biomedical Laboratory, Whiting-Turner Contracting Co. - change order; 020328-01 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - YPB 204-210 Clinic Renovations, Charles Beckman Swanson Architects- Doc Y 130-A; 020404-01 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - YPB 204-210 Clinic Renovations, Charles Beckman Swanson Architects- Doc Y105; 020404-01 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - YPB 204-210 Clinic Renovations, Chapel Construction- Change Order; 020404-01 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - YPB 204-210 Clinic Renovations, Chapel Construction- Contract for Construction Phase; 020404-01 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Mason Laboratory Abestos Removal and Containment, Baddidge- Change Order; 020404-02 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Mason Laboratory Abestos Removal and Containment, Baddidge- Doc Y-202; 020404-02 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - YPB Basement air handling, Chapel Construction - change order; 020412-02 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - YPB Basement air handling, Chapel Construction - contract; 020412-01 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - HLH fan coil unit replacement, Annex Mechanical - Doc Y215; 020412-04 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - FMB, LH, BML 2nd floor corridor, Payette Associates - Agreement for ARchitectural Services; 020424-01 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - MS Research, Fusco - change orders; 020425-01 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - TMP, Babbidge - change order; 020430-01 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - TMP, Babbidge - contract; 020430-01 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - YSM standby power phase 3, Whiting-Turner - change order; 020508-01 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - JESFC back-up hot water system, Annex Mechanical - Doc Y215 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - JE Dining Hall Servery, S. Monaco - change order; 020522-01 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - JE Dining Hall Servery, S. Monaco - doc Y215 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - YSM South Frontage Site, Turner Construction - change order; 020530-01 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - YSM South Frontage Site, Turner Construction - contract; 020530-01 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - YSM FMB 201-203 LH222, Whiting-Turner - change order 1-3; 020530-02 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - YSM FMB 201-203 LH222, Whiting-Turner - Payette Associates - contract; 020530-02 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Campus sidewalk/landscape maint., J.F.K. Kelly - Abb. Agr. for Const. Proj.; 020531-01 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Campus sidewalk/landscape maint., Elmer Laydon Construction - Abb. Agr. for Constr. Proj.; 020531-01 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - BML 326/330 330A, Taulman Construction - change order no. 1; 020604-01 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - BML 326/330 330A, Taulman Construction-Kenneth Boroson # Arch. - contract; 020604-01 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - SDQ parking lot replacement, Daniel O'Connell's Sons - Certificate of Substantial Completion; 020611-01 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Pierson College telecom/power enabling, Linbeck/Kennedy & Rossi - CHANGE ORDER NO. 1; 020606-02 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Pierson College telecom/power enabling, Linbeck/Kennedy & Rossi - contract; 020606-02 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - BAC elevator modernization, Hontz Elevator - change order no. 1; 020612-01 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - BAC elevator modernization, Hontz Elevator - contract; 020612-01 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - BRBL pipe riser replacement, Buckingham Routh - Doc Y215; 021126-01 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - ML 219 lab renovation, S. Monaco - Doc Y215; 021217-01 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - KGL Room 321 A-C, Business Invirons - Doc Y215; 030108-01 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - KGL Rooms 208-209 lab renovation, Business Invirons - Doc Y215; 030620-01 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 246 Church St. basement, Business Invirons - Doc Y215; 030624-01 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Becton 611B lab renovation, Petra Construction - Doc Y215; 030626-01 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Armory heating system replacement, Annex Mechanical - Doc Y215; 030626-02 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - KGL Machine Shop relocation, K. Zampa Construction - Doc Y215; 030715-01 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 52 Hillhouse basement renovation, Giordano Construction - Doc Y215; 031027-01 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - LSOG/LCI Tunnel asbestos abatement, Petco Insulation - Doc Y215; 031107-01 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - SHM Tunnel asbestos abatement, Petco Insulation - Doc Y215; 031107-02 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Medical School A - B Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020213-01, 020326-01, 030715-02, 020604-01 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Medical School CA- CS Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030328-01, 030403-01, 030718-01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Medical School Ce Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020308-02, 011023-01 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Medical School Co Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040202-01, 980518-01, 020729-01 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Medical School E Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031212-01, 030804-02, 011015-01, 030909-02, 980515-03 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Medical School F Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 021211-01, 040427-01, 031103-03 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Medical School G Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020705-01, 020712-01, 030725-01 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Medical School H Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 000916-02, 031006-02, 100651-2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Medical School L Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030227-01, 030205-01, 021030-01, 021213-01, 021031-01, 030403-04, 040303-01, 040329-01 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Medical School M Sterling Hall of Medicine B Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030425-01, 980324-03, 031023-01, 040108-01, 00113-01 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Medical School Sterling Hall of Medicine C Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030717-01 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Medical School Sterling Hall of Medicine I Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020524-01, 03110511, 030813-02, 030118-01, 031216-01, 010724-01, 020111-01, 030815-03, 021008-02, 021122-01, 010726-04 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Medical School Sterling Hall of Medicine L - En Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031030-01, 100648-9, 020924-01 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Medical School T Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030923-01, 030610-02, 010726-01, 040305-01 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Medical School YARC Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040520-01, 020226-01, 030915-01, 040114-02 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Medical School YPB Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020404-01, 020412-02, 020308-01, 011130-02, 011211-01, 010301-02, 000706-01, 011114-02, 031006-03, 011126-01 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Medical School YSM Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020904-02, 030917-01 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Medical School A-B Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 003150-4, 100649-7, 100648-5, G0000066, G0000062, 100650-0 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Medical School C Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 100648-4, G0000039, G0000063, 003151-0 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Medical School E-H Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 100650-7, 003151-4, 100648-8, G0000058, 100647-8, G0000064, G0000060, 100651-2, 100651-8 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Medical School L Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 100648-9, 100651-5, G0000059, 003150-1, 003149-2, 003146-0 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Medical School M-N Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 003152-9, 100650-6 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Medical School S Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 003149-0, 003152-7, 003146-0, 100649-3, 100648-2, 100651-1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Medical School T-YARC Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 003151-6, 003202-1, 100649-5, 003149-2, 100649-0 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Medical School YPB-YSM Non Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004; 100647-7, 003149-8, 100649-2, 100650-2, 003149-7, 100651-0, 003152-5, 003150-0, 003149-5, G0000065 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Central/Science PWG Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020212-01, 030926-01, 040312-02, 040524-01 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Central/Science R Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031114-02, 031007-01 (Box 5A, Folder 1)
  - Central/Science SCL Room 168 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030729-01 (Box 5A, Folder 2)
  - Central/Science SCL SPL OML Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040416-01 (Box 5A, Folder 3)
  - Central/Science SDQ Adaptive Reuse Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 960509-01 (Box 5A, Folder 4)
  - Central/Science Sterling Law Building High St. Wing Damage Repair Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030604-01 (Box 5A, Folder 5)
  - Central/Science Sterling Law Building York St. Offices Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040318-01 (Box 5A, Folder 6)
  - Central/Science SM Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-43, 980224-22 (Box 5A, Folder 7)
  - Central/Science SML Book Stacks Envir Improve Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031031-02; 930517-04 (Box 5A, Folder 8)
  - Central/Science SML renovation, Shepley Bulfinch Richardson and Abbott - change authorization request; 930517-04 (Box 5A, Folder 8)
  - Central/Science SML Steam Trap Replacement Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031202-01 (Box 5A, Folder 9)
  - Central/Science SML Wall Street buttress rehab, Shepley Bulfinch Richardson and Abbott - change authorization request; 980224-18 (Box 5A, Folder 9)
  - Central/Science SML Music Library, Shepley Bulfinch Richardson and Abbott - change authorization request; 941031-2 (Box 5A, Folder 9)
  - Central/Science SOM Donaldson Commons Fire Alarm Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031031-03 (Box 5A, Folder 10)
  - Central/Science SPL Lab B 20 Water Upgrade Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031112-01 (Box 5A, Folder 11)
  - Central/Science SPL Passenger Elevator Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 010606-01 (Box 5A, Folder 12)
  - Central/Science SPL Rooms 16 and 18 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2010; 040618-05 (Box 5A, Folder 13)
  - BRBL/Hewitt Plaza Landscape - Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 031002-08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - BECTON 611B Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 030626-01 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - BASS Vacuum Pump Replace CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 031031-01 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - BAC Computer Room Relocation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 030603-02 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - BAC Inergen System- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040406-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Admin Reno 35- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030311-01 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - BAC Compact Shelving, Phase 2- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030408-01 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Arts Area, Ph II, Conc. Pgmg and Planning- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 980910-01 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ARMORY Install Fire Alarm System CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 031103-02 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - ARMORY Heating System Replacement- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030626-02 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Betts House Exterior Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030626-03 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Beinecke/Hewitt Plaza Rehab- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 010215-01 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - BECTON Transformer Replacement- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 030314-01 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - BECTON 611B Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030626-01 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Beinecke/Hewitt Plaza Rehab- Purchase Orders F/Y-03; 010215-01 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Becton 224-227 Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 020802-02 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - BECTON 204 Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 021114-01 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - BRBL / SML Room B50 Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 021206-01 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - BRBL Space Study- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040401-01 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - ARMORY Heating System Replacement- Purchase Orders F/Y-04; 030626-02 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Cen/Sci Steam Distrib. System Upgr, Ph 6- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 030527-01 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Cen/Sci Tunnel Asbestos Abate., Ph 4- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 020501-02 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Central Steam and Chilled Water Distr. Sys- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030404-01 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Central Auto Shut Down System CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y-03; 030812-02 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Campus Sidewalk Landscape Maintenance- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 030602-01 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Campus Sidewalk Landscape Maintenance 04- Purchase Orders F/Y-04; 030602-01 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Campus Sign System, Phase 2- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030804-01 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Campus Sign System- Purchase Orders F/Y-03-04; 991210-02 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Campus Sidewalk/Landscape Maintenance- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 020531-01 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Chemistry Research Bldg Utilities Svcs- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 021219-02 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - CHUR246 Basement Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 030624-01 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Chemistry Research Building- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 000121-02 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - CRWN341 Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 020913-01 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - DL Room 124 Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040113-01 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - DC Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y-; 980223-77 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Coxe CAGE Indoor Track- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 020403-01 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - College St. Retainer Wall- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 010319-03 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - CULLMAN Fire Alarm System Install CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 031031-04 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - DL Undergrad Space Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y-; 020321-02 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Durfee Hall Trash Area- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 010319-01 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - DW Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y-04; 000630-01 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - MCDB Research Building- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 000127-02 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Library Shelving Facility, Ph. 2- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 010125-01 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Leigh Hall Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 020222-01 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Lapham Field House Boiler Replacement- Purchase Orders F/Y-03; 021217-03 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - LWR Interior Rehabilitation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 021119-01 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - LOCK63 Acquisition- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 980224-31 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Kline Biology Tower 2ND, OML 1st Floor Renovations- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 020920-01 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Kline Biology Tower 442 and 5th Floor Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 020207-01 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - KCL Chem Safety Piping CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040115-01 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - KGL CW System Replace/Modify CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040206-01 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - KGL Machine Shop Relocation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 030715-05 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - KGL Roof Replacement- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 031002-07 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - KGL Room B-20 Ceramic Grinder- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 030919-04 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - KGL Room 117 New Office Space- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040401-02 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - KGL Room 334 Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 031029-01 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Kline Biology Tower 2ND, OML 1st Floor Renovations- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 020920-01 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - KGL Room 321A-C Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030108-01 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - IR Cooler Tower- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040116-03 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - IR Dasher Board System Replacement- Purchase Orders F/Y-03; 030619-01 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - ML 118 Engineering Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 031203-01 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - ML 214 Lab Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030129-01 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - ML Asbestos Containment Study- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 020404-02 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - ML Elevator Modernization- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 980224-01 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - ML Exhaust Fans Removal CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030919-02 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - ML Exhaust Fans Install CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 030908-01 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - ML Room 124 Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 040517-01 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - EDW 309 Miscellaneous Renovations- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 030729-03 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - ELM149 Renovation- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 971023-01 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Engrg Appl Sci Soc Sci Planning Study- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 010402-01 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Engineering Bldg. Steam and Chilled Water- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 030404-01 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Engineering Research Building- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 000120-01 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Environmental Sciences Facility- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03-04; 931115-10 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - ESC 1st Floor Renovations- Purchase Orders F/Y- 04; 031212-01 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - ESC Room 254 Lab Fit-out- Purchase Orders F/Y-03; 030814-01 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - ESC Interconnect Vault Repair CRAF04- Purchase Orders F/Y- 03; 031114-01 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Central/Science SSS 2nd and 4th Floor Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030729-02 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Central/Science SSS 3rd Floor South Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030603-01 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Central/Science SSS Fire Protection Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-41 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Central/Science SSS Room 410 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030729-02 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Central/Science SSS Woolsey and UT accessibility Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040506-01 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Central/Science Saybrook College Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 000407-02 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Central/Science Science Hall Parking Garage Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020321-01 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Central/Science Sterling Divinity Quad. Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 000503-01 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Central/Science TC Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-69 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Central/Science TD Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-56 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Central/Science Temp 370 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-44 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Central/Science Temp 442 Heating Sys. Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040212-01 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Central/Science UHSC Backfill Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031010-01 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Central/Science UHSC Business Office Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 010919-01 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Central/Science UHSC Feasibility Study Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980923-01 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Central/Science UHSC Interim Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030429-01 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Central/Science Undergraduate Astronomy Observatory Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030515-01 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Central/Science University Police Facility Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-07 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Central/Science V- Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-71 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Central/Science WHIT 55 FES Swing Space Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 021106-01 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Central/Science WHIT 155 Computer Room Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030815-02 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Central/Science WHIT 158 Renovation and Addition Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030623-02 (Box 7, Folder 15)